Here's our coding solution for the share action
这就是我们的分享行为提示的代码1解决方法。
provider. Lets start by adding a string. The
让我们从添加字符串来作为开始。
string will be used for the label for our action. Now we're going to add a new
字符串会成为我们的行为的标签。现在我们要添加一个新的
menu resource. This resource will be for the
菜单资源。这些资源会成为
detail fragment. We'll start by adding the name
详细的片段帧。我们将从添加名字空间开始，
space used by the Android support library for
这些名字空间被用于支持安卓语言设计的小部件可扩张标记语言
it's widget XML. Finally, we add the actual item.
最终，我们添加到实际项目中去。
This menu item contains the string that we
这个菜单项目包含我们从
just added from the strings file. It's always字符串文件里面添加的字符串。
shown as an action. So it appears on
它作为一个行为被展示出来。所以它会出现在
the action bar. And it's actionProviderClass, is the ShareActionProvider
行为棒中。它是一行为提示分级，是安卓支持的库里面的一个分享行为提示。
from the Android support library. The Android support
安卓支持的库
library allows the ShareActionProvider to be used on earlier
允许分享行为提示能被使用于比
versions of Android then 4.0. When it was
安卓4.0前的版本。当它
officially added to the framework. Next, let's go to
被官方添加到框架中去。接下来，让我们进入
the DetailAactivity. We're going to be looking at the
详细活动模块。我们即将了解
DetailFragment within the DetailActivity. So the first thing
包含详细活动的细节片段帧。我们要做的第一件事
we can do in our fragment is to add a few useful things. Let's add a log
是在我们的片段帧里面添加一些有用的东西。让我们添加
tag, a string for the share hashtag, hashtag
一个您可以，一个用来分享的井号标签，井号标签阳光应用字符串，
sunshineApp, and we're going to take the forecast
然后添加一个预示字符串
string and make it a member variable. Next
使它成为一个有效成员。接下来
in onCreate view, let's actually populate our member variable.
在onCreate窗口，我们让有效成员实际生成。
And then finally, use it to set the text.
最后，使用它设置文本。
Lets create a share intent. This intent uses ACTION_SEND.
我们创建一个分享指令。这个指令使用ACTION_SEND。
This flag activity cleared when task reset is somewhat
在一些重要时刻当任务被重置时，这些标志活动会被清除。
important. It prevents the activity we're sharing to from
它阻止我们正要分享的活动
being place onto the activity stack. What will happen,
被放入活动栈。
if we don't have this flag, is when you
如果我们没有这个标志，接下来会发生的是
click on the icon to return to the application
当我们点击模块返回应用时，
later, you may actually end up in another application.
你可能实际结束了另一个应用。
The one that's actually handling the share intent. When
真正掌握分享指令是
FLAG_ACTIVITY_CLEAR_WHEN_TASK_RESET is used, it'll actually return you to your
当你使用 FLAG_ACTIVITY_CLEAR_WHEN_TASK_RESET时，它会真正返回你
application instead. We've set the type, test/plain, to let
的当前应用。我们已经设置类型，test/plain，让
Android know we're going to be sharing plain text. And
安卓知道我们即将分享清晰的文本。
then we share our forecast string plus our hashtag.
然后添加我们分享的预示字符串到井号标签。
Only one more thing left to do. We have
最后只剩下一件事要做了。我们
to add the menu to the fragment. To do
要添加一个菜单到片段帧。做完这个，
this, we have to set a flag that this fragment
我们再添加一个标志给这个片段帧赋予
has an options menu at all. Otherwise, it
其一个选择菜单。否则，
won't actually call the onCreate options menu member
它不会有onCreate可选菜单成员结构。
function. Finally, here's our on creat options member
最后，这就是我们的on create 可选成员
function. As you can see, we're inflating the
结构。正如你所见的，我们使一个
detailfragment menu that we created earlier. Finding the
我们早前创建的片段帧菜单生效。找到
share item, getting the ShareActionProvider, and attaching our
分享目录，接着点击分享行为提示，然后链接我们的
intent to this ShareActionProvider. You'll want to update
的指令到分享行为提示。无论什么时候你
this whenever the data you want to share changes.
要分享的数据改变了它都会及时更新。
And that's it. You've now added a ShareActionProvider into Sunshine.
这就是全部内容了。你现在就可以添加一个分享行为提示到sunshine了。